<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour guide</string>
    <!--Main activity-->
    <string name="travel">Quick travel in Italy</string>
    <string name="general_information">General Information</string>
    <string name="rome">Rome</string>
    <string name="milan">Milan</string>
    <string name="turin">Turin</string>
    <string name="naples">Naples</string>
    <string name="bologna">Bologna</string>
    <string name="florencia">Florencia</string>
    <string name="vatican">Vatican</string>
    <string name="pisa">Pisa</string>
    <string name="venice">Venice</string>
    <string name="sicily">Sicily</string>
    <string name="genoa">Genoa</string>
    <string name="about_app">About app</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <!--Main activity-->
    /////////////////
    <!--General information-->
    <string name="italy_1">\tItaly, officially the Italian Republic or Republic of Italy  is a country consisting of a peninsula delimited by the Alps and several islands surrounding it, whose territory largely coincides with the homonyms geographical region. Italy is located in the middle of the Mediterranean Sea, in Southern Europe; it is also considered part of Western Europe. A unitary parliamentary republic with Rome as its capital and largest city, the country covers a total area of 301,230 km2 and shares land borders with France, Switzerland, Austria, Slovenia, as well as the enclaves microstates of Vatican City and San Marino. Italy has a territorial exclave in Switzerland. With around 60 million inhabitants, Italy is the third-most populous member state of the European Union.</string>
    <string name="italy_2">\tRome, a settlement around a ford on the river Tiber in central Italy conventionally founded in 753 BC, was ruled for a period of 244 years by a monarchical system, initially with sovereigns of Latin and Sabine origin, later by Etruscan kings. The tradition handed down seven kings: Romulus, Numa Pompilius, Tullus Hostilius, Ancus Marcius, Tarquinius Priscus, Servius Tullius and Tarquinius Superbus. In 509 BC, the Romans expelled the last king from their city, favouring a government of the Senate and the People (SPQR) and establishing an oligarchic republic. The Roman Empire was among the most powerful economic, cultural, political and military forces in the world of its time, and it was one of the largest empires in world history. At its height under Trajan, it covered 5 million square kilometres.[81][82] The Roman legacy has deeply influenced Western civilisation, shaping most of the modern world; among the many legacies of Roman dominance are the widespread use of the Romance languages derived from Latin, the numerical system, the modern Western alphabet and calendar, and the emergence of Christianity as a major world religion.[83] The Indo-Roman trade relations, beginning around the 1st century BCE, testify to extensive Roman trade in far away regions; many reminders of the commercial trade between the Indian subcontinent and Italy have been found, such as the ivory statuette Pompeii Lakshmi from the ruins of Pompeii.</string>
    <string name="italy_3">\tItaly, whose territory largely coincides with the homonyms geographical region, is located in Southern Europe and it is also considered a part of western Europe,[22] between latitudes 35° and 47° N, and longitudes 6° and 19° E. To the north, Italy borders France, Switzerland, Austria, and Slovenia and is roughly delimited by the Alpine watershed, enclosing the Po Valley and the Venetian Plain. To the south, it consists of the entirety of the Italian Peninsula and the two Mediterranean islands of Sicily and Sardinia (the two biggest islands of the Mediterranean), in addition to many smaller islands. The sovereign states of San Marino and the Vatican City are enclaves within Italy, while Campione Italia is an Italian exclave in Switzerland. The country`s total area is 301,230 square kilometres.</string>
    <string name="italy_4">\tAfter its quick industrial growth, Italy took a long time to confront its environmental problems. After several improvements, it now ranks 84th in the world for ecological sustainability. National parks cover about 5% of the country, while the total area protected by national parks, regional parks and nature reserves covers about 10.5% of the Italian territory, to which must be added 12% of coasts protected by marine protected areas. Extensive traffic and congestion in the largest metropolitan areas continue to cause severe environmental and health issues, even if smog levels have decreased dramatically since the 1970s and 1980s, and the presence of smog is becoming an increasingly rarer phenomenon and levels of sulphur dioxide are decreasing.</string>
    <string name="italy_5">\tItaly is the fifth most visited country in international tourism, with a total of 52.3 million international arrivals in 2016. The total contribution of travel and tourism to GDP (including wider effects from investment, the supply chain and induced income impacts was EUR162.7bn in 2014 (10.1% of GDP) and generated 1,082,000 jobs directly in 2014 (4.8% of total employment). People mainly visit Italy for its rich culture, cuisine, history, fashion, architecture and art. Winter and summer tourism are present in many locations in the Alps and the Apennines, while seaside tourism is widespread in coastal locations on the Mediterranean Sea. Italy is also the country with the highest number of UNESCO World Heritage Sites in the world (58). Rome is the 3rd most visited city in Europe and the 12th in the world, with 9.4 million arrivals in 2017 while Milan is the 27th worldwide with 6.8 million tourists. In addition, Venice and Florence are also among the world`s top 100 destinations.</string>
    <string name="italy_6">\tItaly is considered one of the birthplaces of western civilization and a cultural superpower. Divided by politics and geography for centuries until its eventual unification in 1861, Italy`s culture has been shaped by a multitude of regional customs and local centres of power and patronage. Italy has had a central role in Western culture for centuries and is still recognised for its cultural traditions and artists. During the Middle Ages and the Renaissance, a number of courts competed to attract architects, artists and scholars, thus producing a legacy of monuments, paintings, music and literature. Despite the political and social isolation of these courts, Italy has made a substantial contribution to the cultural and historical heritage of Europe. Italy has rich collections of art, culture and literature from many periods. The country has had a broad cultural influence worldwide, also because numerous Italians emigrated to other places during the Italian diaspora. Furthermore, Italy has, overall, an estimated 100,000 monuments of any sort (museums, palaces, buildings, statues, churches, art galleries, villas, fountains, historic houses and archaeological remains), and according to some estimates the nation is home to half the world`s art treasures.</string>
    <string name="italy_7">\tThe most popular sport in Italy is football. Italy`s national football team is one of the world`s most successful teams with four FIFA World Cup victories (1934, 1938, 1982 and 2006). Italian clubs have won 48 major European trophies, making Italy the second most successful country in European football. Italy`s top-flight club football league is named Serie A and is followed by millions of fans around the world. Other popular team sports in Italy include basketball, volleyball, bicycle racing and rugby. Motorsports are also extremely popular in Italy. Italy has won, by far, the most MotoGP World Championships. Italian Scuderia Ferrari is the oldest surviving team in Grand Prix racing, having competed since 1948, and statistically the most successful Formula One team in history with a record of 232 wins. The Italian Grand Prix of Formula 1 is the fifth oldest surviving Grand Prix, having been held since 1921. It is also one of the two Grand Prix present in every championship since the first one in 1950.[548] Every Formula 1 Grand Prix (except for the 1980) has been held at Autodromo Nazionale Monza. Formula 1 was also held at Imola (1980–2006, 2020) and Mugello (2020). Other successful Italian car manufacturers in motorsports are Alfa Romeo, Lancia, Maserati and Fiat.</string>
    <!--General information-->
    /////////////////
    <!--Rome-->
    <string name="rome_1">\tThe Flavian Amphitheater, commonly known as the Colosseum, is one of the greatest achievements of antiquity.  A stadium in the center of Rome that could seat between 45k – 80k spectators and feed their thirst for blood. The Colosseum was used to entertain the inhabitants of Rome.  Sometimes games were state-sponsored or privately sponsored as a political or power play. The Colosseum is in incredible shape for being an almost 2000-year-old building that has been pillaged and stripped for parts. Visiting the Colosseum is easy under normal circumstances with the exception of long lines.  Your admission ticket also includes the Palatine Hill and Roman Forum which we have featured on this list. There are different levels of access for the Colosseum from general admission to Underground and other restricted area access like the Arena Floor and Top Tiers.  We definitely recommend a guided tour of the Colosseum and have options for any price-range.  If you travel across the world to visit Rome, this is the epicenter of your trip!</string>
    <string name="rome_2">\tThe Roman Forum is the best look into the world of the ancient Romans.  A sophisticated and cultured society that brought the world many steps closer to modernization and brought many cultures together. Yes, Rome was a fighting nation, but the reason they grew as a society was their ability to politic and include conquered nations after defeat.  You could join Rome and prosper or continue to rebel and they’d sow salt into your land and pillage your towns. The Roman Forum was home to many of Rome’s major temples and places of commerce.  It was also home to the famed Senate house where politicians would decide the fate of Rome. Today, its a well preserved archaeological site that is down-right cool.</string>
    <string name="rome_3">\tThe Pantheon was one of Rome’s greatest structures and the best-preserved structure from antiquity without argument. The building survives today as a Catholic Church, Santa Maris degli Angeli e dei Martiri, but was originally a pagan temple. The name may mean “Of All The Gods” but there is much speculation around that. Construction began at the beginning of the 2nd century under the rule of Emperor Hadrian and inaugurated about ten years after. The facade reads, “Marcus Agrippa, Son of Lucius, Built This in His 3rd Time Console.” Marcus Agrippa did in fact build the original structure, but it was like comparing a barn to the Eiffel Tower. The original structure, commissioned by Marcus Agrippa, burnt down twice due to its wood construction. Hadrian commissioned the current structure out of stone which is why it has passed the test of time.</string>
    <string name="rome_4">\tThe word Belvedere (Bell – vey – dare – ā) literally translates to a beautiful view and that is exactly what you’ll get.  There are many amazing natural viewpoints in Rome but Gianicolo hill beats them all. Located on the west side of Rome’s center, Gianicolo Hill is a favorite for all Romans.  Take a loved one up there for a viewpoint date or go with friends and make good conversation.  There is normally a stand that sells crappy sandwiches and overpriced beer you can buy from and enjoy the view over a drink and bite to eat.</string>
    <string name="rome_5">\tTrajan’s column is an incredible monument and surviving piece of propaganda from the 2nd century AD. The column has an incredible history and plays a very important role in our ability to put together ancient timelines.The column, built in approximately 113 AD, honors Emperor Trajan for his conquests in Dacia or modern-day Romania. It is located in Trajan’s Forum, also dedicated to the late emperor, and is 114 feet tall (35 meters).</string>
    <string name="rome_6">\tThe quiet, medieval village of Rocca Massima is an unlikely home for a thrilling zipline. Zip through 2 kilometers of zipline 730 meters above the picturesque village for stunning views of the village and nearby slopes, peaking at 160 kph! If you need to hold someone’s hand, you can ride as a tandem.</string>
    <string name="rome_7">\tInventor. Scientist. Artist. Engineer. Architect. Renaissance man. Da Vinci is definitely on the podium as one of history’s greatest brainiacs! Follow his story and step into his mind at this museum to see just how much he did, including 65 working wooden models of his inventions created by the da Vinci codes! Whether you opt for a museum visit, exhibition tour, or VIP experience, an insightful day is guaranteed.</string>
    <!--Rome-->
    ////////////////
    <!--Milan-->
    <string name="milan_1">\tMilan Cathedral, called Duomo di Milano in Italian, is one of the world’s largest Gothic cathedrals, located in the heart of the city. Milan Cathedral, called Duomo di Milano in Italian, is a vast Gothic-style cathedral, located in the heart of Milan. It is 515 ft (157 metres) long and 302 ft (92 m) wide. It can house up to 40.000 people. Il Duomo di Milano is one of the largest Catholic churches in the world. Il Duomo di Milano is one of the most important attractions in Milan and is well worth visiting. Moreover, climbing to the top of the rooftop terrace offers breath-taking views of the city. However, the Treasure is not as recommendable as the other parts of the Cathedral.</string>
    <string name="milan_2">\tLake Como is a beautiful and peaceful inland sea surrounded by picturesque villages and hamlets: a great place to spend a relaxing and charming holiday. Also known as Lake Lario (from its Latin name: Larius Lacus), Lake Como is shaped like an inverted letter “Y”, with three large arms; to the west is the town of Como, to the east is Lecco and to the north is Colico. Lake Como’s charming villages. Lake Como has numerous charming villages.</string>
    <string name="milan_3">\tThe Archduke Ferdinand of Austria-Este commissioned the construction of a new Ducal Theatre when a fire burnt down the previous theatre in 1776. The opera house was built on the site where the former site of the Church Santa Maria alla Scala, hence the name of the Teatro alla Scala. Like other theatres of the same period, La Scala also housed a casino during its early years. In 1943, during World War II, the theatre was badly damaged by bombing. It was reconstructed three years later. In 2002, the Opera House was closed for two years while it was renovated and opened in November 2004 with an opening performance of Europa riconosciuta by Antonio Salieri, which is the same opera that was performed when the theatre was inaugurated in 1778.</string>
    <string name="milan_4">\tThe structure built between 1865 and 1877 is formed by two arcades shaped like a Latin cross covered by a glass and iron dome. The Galleria is located between two of the main monuments in Milan: il Duomo and the Teatro alla Scala. In our opinion, this magnificent shopping arcade is one of the most interesting sights in Milan. The Galleria Vittorio Emanuele II contains brands such as Prada, Gucci and Louis Vuitton, as well as other high-end boutiques. It also houses numerous well-decorated restaurants, including some of the oldest establishments of Milan such as Café Biffi, founded in 1867. Surprisingly, visitors can also find a McDonald’s in the Gallery. This said, the fast-food restaurant is beautifully decorated with black columns and gold decoration to blend in with the other establishments. It has a comfortable terrace to sit in and have an inexpensive drink, while enjoying the atmosphere and elegance of this stunning building.  </string>
    <string name="milan_5">\tThe Piazza Gael Aulenti and the surrounding buildings are the result of the regeneration of the neighbourhoods Garibaldi, Isola and Varesine. The area is a mix between the city’s historic centre and the financial district. The redevelopment plan was directed by the Argentine architect Cesar Pelli and its main nucleus is the Piazza Gael Aulenti, elevated 6 meters above the street. The square is surrounded by various buildings, all with a surprising design. The most impressive is the 231-meters tall Discredit Tower, which is currently the highest skyscraper in Italy.</string>
    <string name="milan_6">\tIf you think Italians are passionate, just wait until you pack into San Siro Stadium to watch a football match. Especially if you manage to get tickets for the Derby della Madonnina, also known as the Milan derby, between A.C. Milan and Inter, both of which consider San Siro to be their home stadium. This massive football shrine–it’s one of the largest stadiums in Europe and the largest in Italy–is a testament to the popularity of both A.C. Milan and Inter. The stadium was consistently enlarged over the first half of the 20th century to accommodate more and more fans, eventually reaching a capacity of around 80,000 people. Now imagine the roar of 80,000 people when a winning goal is scored–that’s what you call passion.</string>
    <string name="milan_7">\tTrain travel is romanticised, but rightly so. There’s something about watching the world go by from a train window. The transportation authority in Milan has capitalised on this idea, turning two of the city’s historic trams into restaurants on wheels that offer lunch and dinner runs. It’s pure joy to eat your way through a five-course menu as the tram rumbles around Milan. The food is nothing to write home about, but crisscrossing the city gives you a glimpse of all of Milan’s greatest hits and where they’re located. Plus, the tram’s historic interiors, like its glass lanterns and upholstered benches, transport you back in time. Just don’t be late–this is the one place in Milan where reservation times are strictly enforced.</string>
    <!--Milan-->
    ////////////////
    <!--Turin-->
    <string name="turin_1">\tLooking at Egyptian mummies and art may seem like one of the more unusual things to do in Turin, Italy, but, you won`t find a better collection anywhere outside of Cairo, and it is Turin`s most visited attraction. The Palazzo dell`Accademia delle Scienze houses the Egyptian Museum, whose collections began in 1824 when King Carlo Felice acquired 5,268 artifacts excavated in Egypt. These were supplemented by later expeditions, and today, the collections contain statues of various gods and of pharaohs of the New Kingdom, including Rameses II and King Thutmose III, along with papyruses, painted linens, a group of Shawabti figures and a Shawabti box, canopic vessels, mummies and sarcophagi, and two tomb chambers from Thebes.</string>
    <string name="turin_2">\tStrictly for football (soccer) fans and a must-see for followers of Turin`s Juventus, the stadium is officially called the Allianz Stadium, but in Turin it`s simply known as The Stadium. You can visit to see the museum and take a guided tour through the facilities, visiting the locker rooms, press box, and the pitch itself (but not a chance to sit in the stands). Tours are offered in English, and exhibits in the museum are labeled in English, as well. In it you can see the trophy room, uniforms, memorabilia, and a film about the team and its fans. The shop is filled with Juv souvenirs. Note that the museum and stadium tour require separate tickets; one does not include the other.</string>
    <string name="turin_3">\tThe National Automobile Museum provides a comprehensive survey of the development of the motor car, with special attention to the Turin auto manufacturers, but by no means limited to them. The collection of antique and classic cars is outstanding, and multimedia exhibits tell their stories and put automobiles in a social and cultural context as well. Among the cars you`ll see here are multiple models of FIAT and Alfa Romeo, plus Italian makers Ferrari, Lancia, Maserati, Auto Bianchi, and Bugati. But you`ll also find examples of Jaguar, Rolls Royce, Mercedes Benz, even a Packard Super 8 and a BMW Isetta.</string>
    <string name="turin_4">\tTurin is a city of beautiful squares and avenues, but no place is lovelier than the arcaded Piazza San Carlo, surrounded by arcaded buildings and punctuated at one end by the matching facades of the churches of Santa Cristina and San Carlo. Beneath the arcades are some of Turin`s most stylish shops and the historic cafés where Italy`s Risorgimento was plotted in the mid-1800s.</string>
    <string name="turin_5">\tWhen you need a break from sumptuous palaces and grand architecture or are looking for free things to do in Turin, stroll toward the river and into the long green Parco Valentino. Here, you`ll find Turin`s own "folly" – a complete "medieval" village, an imaginative view of what one might have looked like, complete with its own castle, artisans` studios, and shops. Built for an exhibition in 1884, the borgo became such a local favorite that it has been maintained as part of the park.</string>
    <string name="turin_6">\tThe Alps have a strong presence in Turin – you can easily spot their snow-capped peaks from a number of popular shopping streets in the city. During the winter, Torinesi go skiing at spots around the Via Lattea; come summertime, families head there to escape the city’s intense humidity. Whether you opt to explore the region by car or on foot, set out early in the morning for Pian del Colle, a tiny hamlet close to the border with France. From here, head uphill towards Les Granges de la Vallée Etroite, following the main road (or the trail through the forest that hugs the road if on foot). At an altitude of 1776 metres, sit down to a hearty lunch of cheesy, silky polenta topped with sausage  alongside a generous beer at Rifugio I Re Magi.</string>
    <string name="turin_7">\tCrowning the mountain of Monte Pirchiriano, the Sacra di San Michele is a striking abbey built around 987 AD. Just 40 kilometres from Turin, it was originally a Benedictine monastery, later abandoned for a couple of centuries before being taken over in 1836 by the Savoys. The peak sits at 962 metres, with sweeping views of the Susa Valley below. On your way back to town, swing past Birrificio San Michele, a brewery at the foot of the mountain, for a platter of salamis and a flight of their craft beers.</string>
    <!--Turin-->
    ////////////////
    <!--Naples-->
    <string name="naples_1">\tNaples has been inhabited for almost 3,000 years and much of the city’s past is hidden beneath the modern streets. Secure your spot on an official Naples Underground (Napoli Sotterranea) tour, the only way to venture below ground and explore the city’s buried history. Admire the ancient Neapolitan aqueduct and WWII air raid shelters</string>
    <string name="naples_2">\tVisit the island of Capri on this 8-hour tour from either Naples or Sorrento. You`ll travel across the sea on a jetfoil boat to reach Capri, where you`ll then enjoy a separate private boat tour to see caves, the Faraglioni rock formations, and other natural attractions. Go swimming in the emerald waters, and take the island`s funicular to Piazza Umberto I, aka La Piazzetta.</string>
    <string name="naples_3">\tA visit to the National Archeological Museum in Naples will surely whet your appetite for seeing the city`s almost more famous neighbor, Pompeii. Several centuries of excavations have uncovered homes, shops, temples, and public buildings of a prosperous city of 20,000 engulfed and frozen in time by the cataclysmic eruption of Vesuvius in AD 79.</string>
    <string name="naples_4">\tUnlike neighboring Pompeii, the Roman resort town of Herculaneum was engulfed by molten lava instead of ash in the AD 79 eruption of Mt. Vesuvius, and its buildings were supported by the lava as it rose in depth. The difference had two results: organic materials were preserved in a dry airtight environment, and the cooled stone was so deep and hard that the site was protected from early plunder until modern techniques and sensibilities could preserve its treasures. What you see today gives an even more intimate view of Roman life than Pompeii.</string>
    <string name="naples_5">\tRearing abruptly out of the plain, 15 kilometers southeast of Naples on the shores of the bay of Naples, Vesuvius is the only volcano on the European mainland that is still intermittently active. It is best known, of course, for the disastrous eruption in AD 79 that destroyed both Pompeii and Herculaneum. Its last major eruption was in 1944, and there have been signs of only mild activity since. Drive or take a bus from Pompeii or Herculaneum to the Vesuvius National Park lot at about 1,000 meters altitude. Trails lead up the final 200 meters to the rim, which can be followed along its entire perimeter. As you would expect, the views are spectacular.</string>
    <string name="naples_6">\tThe southern coast of the Amalfi Peninsula, south of Naples, is among the most beautiful in all Europe, with colorful villages clinging to steep mountainsides that drop almost straight into the blue waters of the Mediterranean. There are several ways to see this coast: by car, bus, boat, or organized tour. While of these a car gives you more freedom to stop and explore on your own (bus schedules make it difficult to spend any time in the towns), the road is narrow and demands 100 percent attention from the driver at all times.</string>
    <string name="naples_7">\tAbout 30 kilometers south of the city, on the Bay of Naples, Castellammare di Stabia is adjacent to the ancient city of Stabiae, destroyed by the AD 79 eruption of Vesuvius. You can visit the excavated Roman villas, which were very well preserved by the "rain" of volcanic ash that buried them. Frescoes and mosaics are intact, as is the swimming pool in its colonnaded atrium. A cable car from the Castellammare Circumvesuviana station climbs Monte Faito, from whose summit there are walking trails and magnificent views of the Bay of Naples and Vesuvius.</string>
    <!--Naples-->
    ////////////////
    <!--Florence-->
    <string name="bologna_1">\tIt may seem as though everyone in Bologna were meeting friends at the same time in these two adjoining squares in the heart of the city. Conversation and laughter blend with the sound of water splashing in the magnificent Neptune Fountain, which gives Piazza del Nettuno its name. Created by Giambologna in the 16th century, it is one of the finest fountains of its period. Nearly every major attraction in the city is within a few minutes` walk, as are the most important streets – among them the busy shopping street, Via dell`Indipendenza, and Via Galleria with its many old aristocratic mansions.</string>
    <string name="bologna_2">\tPisa`s may be more famous, but Bologna has a pair of towers that appear to tilt even more alarmingly because of their narrow shape. They are the best-known of the 20 towers that remain of the more than 100 that formed Bologna`s 12th-century skyline. Although they were necessary as both watchtowers and places of refuge in case of attack, their height also became status symbols for the noble families that built them. The 48-meter Torre Garisenda leans by more than 13 meters; you can climb the 498 steps inside Torre degli Asinelli for bird`s-eye views of Bologna.</string>
    <string name="bologna_3">\tThe Pinacoteca has a unique mission: to preserve and display works by artists who have lived and worked in Bologna and the Emilia-Romagna region, especially from the 13th to the early 19th centuries. Some of the works have histories of their own, many have been rescued from churches that were closed or turned to other uses, and others have been returned to Bologna after Napoleon I carried them off to the Louvre in Paris. The museum collections include works by Raphael, Perugino, Tintoretto, and other Renaissance artists.</string>
    <string name="bologna_4">\tThe basilica stands atop a hill that commands views across the city and the Po Valley landscape, its classical interior highlighted by the striking floor of inlaid black, white, and red marble floor. The chancel is lined in equally striking variegated black and white marble. But what distinguishes this basilica from all the others in Italy is the 3.8-kilometer covered arcade that connects the sanctuary to the city. This monumental structure is the longest portico in the world, with 666 arches, and was built between 1674 and 1793 to protect the Byzantine Madonna with Child icon in its annual procession into Bologna. The icon, said to have been painted by Saint Luke, has traveled this route to Bologna`s Cathedral of San Pietro since 1433, when it was brought from a hilltop convent in the hope of a miracle to stop harvest-threatening rains.</string>
    <string name="bologna_5">\tVisitors to Bologna can`t help strolling under the portici, the arcades that line so many of its streets. They are a welcome relief from the summer sun and shelter from the rain, as well as providing extra space to shops, which often display goods under them. They began in the 11th century as overhanging upper stories of buildings in the growing city center, adding more living and storage space over the shops and businesses on the street level. As they became larger, they needed support beams and posts, and gradually the arcades grew. In the 13th century, new arcades were required to be tall enough for a rider to pass through on horseback, a rule that led to the elegant arched arcades we see today.</string>
    <string name="bologna_6">\tPerhaps Bologna`s greatest appeal to tourists, and the source of its fame throughout Italy, is its reputation as a culinary center. It`s known for tortellini, tagliatelle, and other pastas, and its classic dish, tagliatelle al ragu, is known elsewhere simply as tagliatelle Bolognese. Cured meats are a local specialty, and this region is the home of the incomparable Parmigiano Reggiano cheese. You can experience and savor Bologna`s culinary heritage. A good place to begin is in its markets and food shops. The narrow streets of the Quadrilatero, an area between Piazza Maggiore, via Rizzoli, via Castiglione, and via Farini, has been a market since Roman times, filled with little shops and outdoor stands selling all kinds of food, from garden produce, cheese, and fish to freshly made pastas and baked goods.</string>
    <string name="bologna_7">\tTortellini is one of the most popular traditional Italian foods in Bologna and most local restaurants will serve this tantalizing dish. Traditionally, Tortellini ring shaped pasta is filled with various stuffing’s such as pork, prosciutto and cheese, and served in a form of chicken or beef broth. Mystery and intrigue surround the origins of this food but Bologna is considered to be one of the best places to experience an authentic Tortellini dish. Consider frequenting one of the restaurants surrounding the Piazza Maggoire, or venturing down the side streets to find a local eatery not geared towards tourists.</string>
    <!--Florence-->
    ////////////////
    <!--Florence-->
    <string name="florence_1">\tPossibly the most celebrated cathedral in the world, the Duomo as it is simply known in Florence is the jewel of the city. It was initially constructed in 1436, but the astonishing front facade wasn’t completed until the 19th century. Located in the center of the old city, the Duomo stands out for miles and creates an imposing sight amongst the other medieval buildings. The exterior and front facade of the Cathedral are monumental – covered in white marble and red, pink and green polychrome designs; the colour and style is breathtaking. Furthermore, an immense dome sits at the read of the cathedral and can be accessed via a series of steps. Although the interior of the cathedral is quite bare in contrast, it still speaks of grandeur and has several interesting pieces such as the large clock face and the magnificent Last Judgement fresco that covers the underside of the dome.</string>
    <string name="florence_2">\tLocated on the Southern Banks of the River Arno, the Palazzo Pitti has stood since the 1400’s as a fine example of Renaissance architecture. A grand square sits at the front of the palace and frames the symmetrical front facade perfectly. Although once home to Italian royalty and powerful families such as the Medici’s, the palace now stands as the largest museum complex in Florence. Inside the palace, there are a myriad of different galleries that are all richly decorated, but also contain a host of Renaissance artwork. The Jupiter room for example contains some amazing frescos but also the famous Veiled Lady by Raphael. Other well-known artists featured include Titian, Rubens, Caravaggio and Vernonese.</string>
    <string name="florence_3">\tConnected to the Palazzo Pitti, the Boboli Gardens are immense and beautiful. Covering an area of 45,000 square meters, the gardens are some of the largest in Florence and are a true delight to walk through. Created in the 16th century, the Boboli Gardens feature a myriad of different sections including a main lawn with a fountain and obelisk, a selection of worldly trees, plants and flowers, and several large ponds complete with water features. If you want to escape the city, you can find solace in this wonderful place and enjoy the beautiful designs and natural specimens.</string>
    <string name="florence_4">\tThis square offers the best view of Florence and of the Cathedral in the entire city. Located on the South banks of the River Arno, the Piazzale Michelangelo sits high on a hill near the Boboli Gardens and the Palazzo Pitti. In the center of the square stands a wonderful Bronze statue of David, and at the edge of the square there is a series of vendors and artists selling their wares. The view from the Piazza is unrivalled and you can truly see Florence in all its glory, framed against the River Arno. If you are looking for a truly memorable photograph, this is the place to be!</string>
    <string name="florence_5">\tThe Vasari Corridor was originally created as a private walkway for Cosimo de Medici from the Palazzo Pitti to the Palazzo Vecchio – The high ranking individuals of Florence during the 1500’s were often reluctant to walk out in the public. Starting at the Palazzo Vecchio, the enclosed corridor stretches alongside the Arno river, and then cross over the Ponte Vecchio and continues on to the Palazzo Pitti on the other side. Inside the corridor there is a host of artwork and refurbished paintings that have been damaged in years past. Although the corridor is currently closed for renovations, you can still marvel at its design and trace its passage from start to finish.</string>
    <string name="florence_6">\tLocated in close proximity to the Piazza del Duomo and the Basilica di San Lorenzo, the Gallery of the Academy of Florence is a hugely important museum. A simple building that you might pass buy if you didn’t know where it was, the Gallery contains some masterpieces of Renaissance art including the original Michelangelo’s David sculpture. Aside from this original piece of genius, the museum also houses other sculptures and works from Michelangelo and is split into several different interesting halls. Here you can find a wealth of historical art, and also a great deal of history pertaining to 14th and 15th century Florence. Finally, there is also a museum of musical instruments that contains a myriad of old and unique musical inventions.</string>
    <string name="florence_7">\tFlorence has some of the best gelato in Italy. Avoid the sellers with bright mountains of artificially coloured gelato and over-the-top garnishes. Small batch is the way to go. Another little secret from a gelato connoisseur is if the colour of the pistachio flavour is anything brighter than a dull greenish brown, keep walking – it’s not good quality, handmade gelato. You deserve better.</string>
    <!--Florence-->
    ////////////////
    <!--Vatican-->
    <string name="vatican_1">\tVatican City, officially the Vatican City State (Italian: Stato della Città del Vaticano; Latin: Status Civitatis Vaticanae), is an independent city-state and enclave located within Rome, Italy. The Vatican City State, also known simply as the Vatican, became independent from Italy with the Lateran Treaty (1929), and it is a distinct territory under "full ownership, exclusive dominion, and sovereign authority and jurisdiction" of the Holy See, itself a sovereign entity of international law, which maintains the city state`s temporal, diplomatic, and spiritual independence. With an area of 49 hectares (121 acres) and a population of about 825, it is the smallest state in the world by both area and population. As governed by the Holy See, the Vatican City State is an ecclesiastical or sacerdotal-monarchical state (a type of theocracy) ruled by the pope who is the bishop of Rome and head of the Catholic Church. The highest state functionaries are all Catholic clergy of various national origins. After the Avignon Papacy (1309–1377) the popes have mainly resided at the Apostolic Palace within what is now Vatican City, although at times residing instead in the Quirinal Palace in Rome or elsewhere.</string>
    <string name="vatican_2">\tThe name "Vatican" was already in use in the time of the Roman Republic for the Ager Vaticanus, a marshy area on the west bank of the Tiber across from the city of Rome, located between the Janiculum, the Vatican Hill and Monte Mario, down to the Aventine Hill and up to the confluence of the Cremera creek. The territory of Vatican City is part of the Vatican Hill, and of the adjacent former Vatican Fields. It is in this territory that St. Peter`s Basilica, the Apostolic Palace, the Sistine Chapel, and museums were built, along with various other buildings. The area was part of the Roman rione of Borgo until 1929. Being separated from the city, on the west bank of the river Tiber, the area was an outcrop of the city that was protected by being included within the walls of Leo IV (847–855), and later expanded by the current fortification walls, built under Paul III (1534–1549), Pius IV (1559–1565), and Urban VIII (1623–1644). When the Lateran Treaty of 1929 that gave the state its form was being prepared, the boundaries of the proposed territory were influenced by the fact that much of it was all but enclosed by this loop. For some tracts of the frontier, there was no wall, but the line of certain buildings supplied part of the boundary, and for a small part of the frontier a modern wall was constructed. The territory includes St. Peter`s Square, distinguished from the territory of Italy only by a white line along the limit of the square, where it touches Piazza Pio XII. St. Peter`s Square is reached through the Via della Conciliazione which runs from close to the Tiber to St. Peter`s. This grand approach was constructed by Benito Mussolini after the conclusion of the Lateran Treaty.</string>
    <string name="vatican_3">\tLeaving St Peter`s Square, take a leisurely stroll through the Vatican Gardens (only authorised tours are allowed). If the weather permits, it is worth visiting the majestic outdoor spaces that occupy almost two-thirds of Vatican City. The Gardens have been the resting place of the Roman Pontiff since 1279. Walking through the Italian or English gardens, you come across playful fountains, streams, temples and caves. Below the Basilica of St Peter, you can visit the necropolis, a Roman cemetery, which is the burial place of St Peter - the first pope. Also located in this area are Vatican Grottoes, which house the tombs of all the popes.4. Museums</string>
    <string name="vatican_4">\tGregorian Egyptian Museum and Gregorian Etruscan Museum were both founded by Pope Gregory XVI in 1839 and 1837 to complete the collection of antiques of the Papal Museums and to give a wide overlook on these two civilisations so important for the development of the Mediterranean culture The Pio Clementino Museum is the heart of the Antique sculpture collection of the Vatican, and one of the first buildings ever designed to be a Museum of Art. The foundation dates back to the papacies of Clement XIV (1769–1774) and Pius VI (1775–1799) but the original collection was housed at the famous Belvedere courtyard already in the Renaissance. Statues like the Laocoon, the Apollo del Belvedere and the Torso have been studied by generations and generations of artist and connoisseurs becoming paramount examples for the development of the canon of beauty into European Art. Chiaramonti Museum is named after Pope Pius VII Chiaramonti, and was opened in 1806 during the dramatic years of the conflict against Napoleon. Many art pieces were brought to France and even the pope himself, in 1809, was imprisoned by the French emperor. With Napoleon’s fall, Antonio Canova, the most famous sculptor of his time, was chosen for the recovery of all art taken away and to display it into this new hall. Around 1,000 pieces of antiques were finally exhibited with a special attention to the extraordinary collection of Roman portrait busts. The New wing was added to the Chiaramonti Gallery when all the art confiscated by the France found his way back to Rome. Architect Raffaele Stern conceived a building that had as its primary objective a better fruition of the works of art. The perfect natural lighting still helps to admire masterpieces like the Augustus of Prima Porta and the Giustiniani Athena.</string>
    <string name="vatican_5">\tVatican Hill (Mons Vaticanus ) is the name given, long before the founding of Christianity, to one of the hills on the side of the Tiber opposite the traditional seven hills of Rome. It may have been the site of an Etruscan town called Vaticum. The name "Vatican" has often been thought to derive from the Latin "vates", meaning "seer, soothsayer", though this is uncertain and it is also possible that "Vaticanus" comes from an unrelated Etruscan loan-word. Indeed, the Vatican Hill was the home of the Vates long before re-Christian Rome. Vaticanus, also known as Vagitanus, was an Etruscan god of prophecy, and his temple was built on the ancient site of Vaticanum (Vatican Hill).</string>
    <string name="vatican_6">\tThe symbol of Vatican City is St Peter`s Square, and it is from this religious place that we recommend you start your visit. The square was designed by Gian Lorenzo Bernini. It is characterised by its elliptical shape and a quadruple row of columns; with a portico above. The 140 statues placed on top of the portico represent the saints. At the centre of the square rests the Vatican Obelisk, behind which stands the largest church in the world, St Peter`s Basilica. The façade is 115 metres wide with the grand `cupolone` perched on top. Look for the central window, the so-called Loggia delle Benedizioni, from which the pope presents the message of good wishes urbi et orbi ("to the city and to the world") immediately after his election, and on the occasion of religious festivities.</string>
    <string name="vatican_7">\tOne of the things you definitely need to take the time to visit, while in the Vatican,  is the St. Peter’s Dome. Once you are up there, a truly breathtaking view of Rome will reveal itself to you.</string>
    <!--Vatican-->
    ////////////////
    <!--Pisa-->
    <string name="pisa_1">\tEvery child has heard of it, and every visitor to Pisa probably heads first to what is undoubtedly the world`s most famous tower: La Torre Pendente, the leaning campanile standing next to the cathedral. The foundation stone was laid in 1173, when Pisa was Italy`s most powerful maritime republic, and its loggia–like tiers were modeled after the cathedral facade. Even before the third story was completed, the tower had already begun to sink alarmingly on its south side. When counter weighting the north side and slightly increasing the height of the south walls proved ineffective, construction was halted. Almost 100 years later, work resumed, attempting to counteract the tilt by angling the upper stories more towards the vertical. The open bell–chamber was added to the white marble tower in 1350–72, by Tommaso Pisano. Until 1990, tourists climbed the spiral staircase of 294 steps to the top platform, but with the angle of tilt increasing by one millimeter a year, it was calculated that the tower would topple by the year 2000. When rotational movement around the axis was also detected, increasing the risk, the tower was closed in 1990 to allow an expensive program of restoration. When the tower re-opened in 2001, the 5.5-degree tilt had been modified to about 3.99 degrees, leaving the top out of line by 3.9 meters. You`ll also notice a slight curve in the tower, resulting from attempts by various architects to correct its tilt during construction.</string>
    <string name="pisa_2">\tThe definitive example of the Pisan architectural style, the Cathedral of Santa Maria Assunta is a five-aisled Romanesque basilica of white marble designed by Pisan architect Buscheto. Begun in 1063, after Pisa`s naval victory over the Saracens, it was consecrated (still unfinished) in 1118, and towards the end of that century, a new west front was added and the main apse was completed. The decorated arcading on the splendid façade is continued round the side walls, and its transepts end in small apses that project well beyond the aisles. Dominating the whole interior is a well-proportioned oval dome. In the apse is a 13th- to 14th-century mosaic of Christ enthroned between the Virgin and John the Evangelist, by Cimabue. Don`t miss the bronze doors of the Porta di San Ranieri, with scenes from the lives of the Virgin and of Christ.</string>
    <string name="pisa_3">\tAccording to local legend, Archbishop Ubaldo dei Lanfranchi returned from the Fourth Crusade with several shiploads of earth from Golgotha, so that the citizens of Pisa could be buried in sacred soil. The construction of the Camposanto (Sacred Field) to hold it began in 1278, a large rectangular cloister whose gallery of arches decorated with Gothic tracery open into the courtyard. On the floor of the cloister are the graves of Pisan patricians, and around the sides are Roman sarcophagi. The walls were covered with 14th- and 15th-century frescoes, but a fire caused by artillery bombardment in 1944 melted the lead roof, either destroying or badly damaging the frescoes.</string>
    <string name="pisa_4">\tThis palace in the Piazza dei Cavalieri (Knights` Square) is also known as the Palazzo della Carovana and was originally the Palazzo degli Anziani (Palace of the Elders). In 1562, architect Giorgio Vasari began rebuilding and enlarging it, creating the magnificent Palazzo dei Cavalieri, named after the training courses for knights (cavalieri) of the Order of St. Stephen, which were held here. The most imposing and ornate building outside of the Piazza dei Miracoli, its facade is decorated with sgraffito ornament; coats of arms; and busts of six Medici Grand Dukes of Tuscany, from Cosimo I to Cosimo III. The grandeur is enhanced by the projecting roof and the handsome double staircase leading up to the entrance. Since 1810, the palazzo has housed the Scuola Normale Superiore, an elite college of higher education founded by Napoleon. In front of the building is a statue of Cosimo I by Piero Francavilla. On the north side of the piazza is the Palazzo dell`Orológio, built in 1607 for the Order of St. Stephen and incorporating the remains of two early medieval tower houses.</string>
    <string name="pisa_5">\tPalazzo Giuli Rosselmini Gualandi, more commonly called Palazzo Blu, houses rich permanent collections of paintings and other art, the works of Italian artists from the 16th to the 20th century. In addition, its collections include fine furniture and early coins. Beyond these collections are a continuing series of special exhibitions that may cover anything from science to cinema, or may feature the works of a single artist, such as M.C. Escher or local favorite, the groundbreaking Italian modernist Amedeo Modigliani.</string>
    <string name="pisa_6">\tAlso known as the Orto Botanico dell`Università di Pisa, Pisa`s botanical garden was the first university botanical garden in Europe, founded by Cosimo I de`Medici in the mid-1500s. You can explore various environments and collections, both outdoors and in its several buildings, to find herb gardens, an arboretum of rare trees, water gardens, and greenhouses. One of these is Europe`s first iron-framed glasshouse. Be sure to see the old botany school dating from the late 1500s, with its facade decorated in seashells. After Pisa`s almost overwhelming abundance of Renaissance artworks, this is a pleasant and restful place to visit in the middle of the city.</string>
    <string name="pisa_7">\tKeith Harring`s last mural ever can also be found in the Tuscan town and can be viewed completely free of charge. The artwork is called Tuttomondo and is one of the few permanent murals by the graffiti artist. You can find the artwork on the facade of the Monastery of San Antonio near Piazza Vittorio Emanuele II. The artwork was created in 1989, just a few months before Harring`s death. It is 180 square meters in size and you will find thirty figures in exactly one week. The symbols stand for peace and tolerance.</string>
    <!--Pisa-->
    ////////////////
    <!--Venice-->
    <string name="venice_1">\tEasily the most renowned and famous building in Venice, St. Mark’s Basilica is a sublime piece of architecture that has stood the test of time since its creation in 1092 and remains one of the most important religious buildings in Northern Italy. Every aspect of this church is fantastic – From the ornate detail, sculptures and artwork of the front facade, to the beautifully painted frescos and Byzantine works of art on the inside of the domed ceiling. Located in the Piazza San Marco, this basilica is easily accessible from the grand canal and is one of the best-known surviving examples of Italian Byzantine architecture.</string>
    <string name="venice_2">\tWhilst St. Mark’s Basilica is the most famous building in Venice, St Mark’s Square is the most famous piazza. Located on the grand canal, opposite the island of San Giorgio Maggiore, this square holds huge importance in Venice and is a truly spectacular place to visit. Surrounding the Piazza is a series of ornate buildings with arched walkways that frame it perfectly. Furthermore, several important buildings are located on the square including St Mark’s Campanile, St Mark’s Basilica, Doge’s Palace and Torre dell’Orologio. This square really is the perfect place to start your tour of Venice and tick off some of its most impressive sights.</string>
    <string name="venice_3">\tVenice has literally hundreds of canals that connect the various islands that make up the city – the largest of which is the Canale Grande. This monumental canal is more like a river and it passes from one side of Venice to the other and snakes through the centre in a large S bend shape. Over 170 buildings dating from as early as the 13th century line the banks of the canal and it has served as an important waterway in the city for hundreds of years. Only four bridges span the grand canal as generally people and tourists travel along the canal, not over it. Consider walking along sections of the canal, admiring the buildings that line it, and watching the busy water traffic of Venice.</string>
    <string name="venice_4">\tAs one of the bridges that spans the impressive Grand Canal, the Ponte di Rialto is undoubtedly the most famous and iconic. Connecting the San Marco and San Polo districts of Venice, the bridge is an important pedestrian thoroughfare, but also a hugely popular tourist attraction. Originally a wooden bridge, this culmination stood for hundreds of years until it collapsed in 1524. After this incident, an ornate stone bridge was built that still stands today. The detail and design of the bridge is simply beautiful and its symmetry perfectly frames the grand canal. Furthermore, the is also a series of shops on the bridge that sell a range of wares from souvenirs to jewellery.</string>
    <string name="venice_5">\tIf you are looking for a spot of relaxation and to get away from the bulk of the tourists, the Lido is the place to go. This separate island creates a barrier between Venice and the Adriatic Sea and features a long stretch of beautiful beach to enjoy. Home to approximately 20,000 inhabitants, the Lido also has a host of residential areas, shops, restaurants and hotels. With a much calmer, laid back and relaxed feeling to central Venice, Lido is a true escape and provides a stark contrast to the busy streets and waterways surrounding the grand canal.</string>
    <string name="venice_6">\tThis is one of the smaller separate islands that is not connected to the main canals of Venice. San Giorgio Maggiore sits a short distance from the Venice Basin and the Grande Canal and can be reached by Vaporetto or private water taxi. Located on the island is the fantastic San Giorgio Monastery, the Church of San Giorgio Maggiore and the large campanile that mirrors the one standing in St. Mark’s Square. Walk through the small harbour and see the various boats moored, visit the fantastic church and monastery, and climb the campanile for amazing views back across to the main city of Venice.</string>
    <string name="venice_7">\tAs the tallest structure in Venice, the campanile is a towering building that stands at a colossal 98.6m high. The building that stands now, is actually a reconstruction as the original collapsed in 1902. Originally created in the 9th century, the campanile was used as a watch tower. Throughout the years, the tower has been damaged by fire, earthquakes and even lightening. Made of a simple red-brick design, the main shaft is quite simple, but the bell housing and pinnacle feature a myriad of arches and stonework, and the top features a golden statue of the Angel Gabriel. Admire the tower from the Piazza di San Marco, but also take the elevator up to the top for possibly the best panoramic views of Venice.</string>
    <!--Venice-->
    ////////////////
    <!--Sicily-->
    <string name="sicily_1">\tI can only start this list of the top things to do in Sicily with the capital, Palermo. It is a very rich city in terms of historical buildings and monuments and the ideal place to visit if you like churches and palaces. In Palermo, you shouldn’t miss: The Norman Palace, Palermo Cathedral, he Massimo Theatre, The Ballaro Market. Not far from Palermo, there is one of the most visited places in Sicily: Monreale Cathedral and its thousands of square meters of golden mosaics. To give you an idea, 2200 kg of pure gold was used to make them!</string>
    <string name="sicily_2">\tThis small fishing town with its colorful boats moored at the pier seems calm and peaceful. OK, I will tell you something, so you will not be disappointed when you will visit Sicily: the reality is nowadays a bit different because Cefalù has become a popular seaside resort. With its sandy beach and medieval alleys, the place is certainly pretty, but quite crowded, especially in high season. I don’t advise you to go there if you only want to enjoy the beach, you will find much better and quieter elsewhere! However, Cefalù is worth a stop to admire the panorama from the old port and pier and stroll through its narrow streets full of shops and restaurants. If you have time, you should also visit the Cefalù Norman cathedral, the most important building of the city.</string>
    <string name="sicily_3">\tLet’s continue this bucket list of things to do in Sicily with Taormina, nicknamed “the Pearl of Sicily”. This town is world-famous for the magnificent view it offers on the plain of Catania, Etna and Isola Bella. It’s one of the most touristic cities in Sicily, so it’s best to go off-season to make the most out of your stay. If you’ve decided to visit the east coast of Sicily, it’s a must-see destination. Here are the things you shouldn’t miss in Taormina: Go down to Isola Bella, the small island and its beach that contribute greatly to the fame of the city and visit Taormina Greek Theatre</string>
    <string name="sicily_4">\tThe Etna volcano is impossible to miss if you are in Sicily. It is one of the island’s main attractions, and it should definitely be included in your tour in Sicily. From Taormina and Catania, many viewpoints allow you to admire it from a distance. But as it’s so close, it would be sad to miss the opportunity to climb up and see its crater, right? The best things to do is to choose a day or half-day excursion. From Catania or Taormina, many tour operators offer full package around 55€ with transport, equipment, guide and 4 Wheel drive vehicle to go up to the crater. Of course you can also drive there, but you will not be supervised, so be careful to have the right shoes and equipment. Check the weather conditions beforehand as well, access is not always allowed. Please note that if you are not accompanied by a guide, you will have to stop at the first level, (after the cable car). To reach the crater, the climb to the second level must be done in a guided minibus.</string>
    <string name="sicily_5">\tThe Valley of the Temples, next to the city of Agrigento, is Sicily best-known archaeological site. It’s the number 1 in terms of visit, before Selinunte Temples and Segesta (I will tell you more about them below). 8 temples are visible in the valley but the 2 best preserved are undoubtedly the temple of Concorde and the temple of Hera. The walk between the temples is very pleasant and easy to do on foot.</string>
    <string name="sicily_6">\tAbout 20 minutes’ drive from the valley of the temples, the Scala dei Turchi is another must-see if your trip to Sicily takes you in this region! This white limestone cliff is famous for its particular shape: it looks like erosion has carved steps! And if you add the turquoise color of the sea and the fine sand beaches that border it, you will understand why Scala dei Turchi is a very popular place.</string>
    <string name="sicily_7">\tWhen you get out of Marsala town, take the salt road that will take you directly to the salt pans. The road then continues to Trapani. The salt pans and their mills are on many postcards, and you will quickly understand why when you will see them! Try to go there at sunset if you can, they are even more photogenic! You can easily stop on the roadside, take a few pictures and maybe buy some of this renowned salt, used by the best Sicilian chefs.</string>
    <!--Sicily-->
    ////////////////
    <!--Genoa-->
    <string name="genoa_1">\tLocated in the centre of the old town in the Molo district, the Piazza De Ferrari is one of the central points of Genoa and offers a myriad of different sights. The main feature of the Piazza is the large ornate fountain – This fountain has a series of water jets that spray into a central basin and forms a lovely symmetrical shape and cascade of water. Surrounding the fountain are a number of important buildings including the Palace of the Doges, the Carlo Felice Theatre, the Genoa stock exchange and the Palace of the Duke of Galleria. Admire the different building and 19th century architecture, throw a coin into the fountain or site and watch the locals go about their business.</string>
    <string name="genoa_2">\tGenoa is known for its once expansive city wall – over the years, the walls were expanded and enclosed much of the city, infact, they were the longest city walls in Italy. Part of this bygone area still stands today in the form of the Porta Soprana gatehouse and towers. These two towers are only a short walk from the Piazza De Ferrari and are easily visible from many parts of the city.</string>
    <string name="genoa_3">\tLocated next to the Piazza Carciamento in the main harbour area, the Aquarium is a brilliant location for all the family. Contained within this building is a myriad of different marine life including varieties of fishes, sharks, dolphins, turtles and Jellyfish. Two central themes are creatures of the Ligurian Sea (the sea that Genoa harbour extends onto) and the environment of the North Atlantic Ocean. All of the displays and tanks are well maintained and spacious, and the environments have been recreated faithfully to give the animals everything they need in terms of climate and habitation.</string>
    <string name="genoa_4">\tAs Genoa was a major naval power during the 16th-19th centuries; it stands to reason that the city should contain one of the largest Maritime museums in Europe. This museum is a truly interesting and insightful place and contains four floors of historical artefacts, reconstructions and displays. One room contains a display of various globes and atlases from different time periods, whilst another hosts a reconstructed galley ship. Alternatively, rooms on the second floor feature reproductions of shipwrecks and a myriad of naval instruments.</string>
    <string name="genoa_5">\tA UNESCO listed World Heritage Site; the Via Garibaldi is one of the most important streets in Genoa and is famous for its large amount of palaces and fine architecture. Notable buildings include the Palazzo Bianco, the Palazzo Rosso, the Palazzo Doria Tursi, the Palazzo Lomelino and the Palazzo Pantaleo. This narrow street provides a staggering amount of fantastic architecture and the most notable building is possible the Palazzo Rosso which features a bright red/orange facade. Three of these palaces are open to the public – Rosso, Bianco and Tursi and offer a great insight into the history of Genoa together with a range of wonderful artefacts and art collections.</string>
    <string name="genoa_6">\tThe Passeggiata Garibaldi is a stretch of paved walkway that winds along the coastline of Genoa. Starting at the Via Giovanni which is approximately 15 minutes to the east of the city centre, the walkway features a pink cobbled path and hugs the coastline perfectly. You can walk this stretch of public footpath for at least 1km through the district of Nervi. Lining the path is a variety of residential buildings, shops and cafes. Come here to escape from the busy city, take in the sea air, and admire the beautiful coastal scenery Genoa has to offer.</string>
    <string name="genoa_7">\tThe Lanterna di Genoa is an ornate ancient lighthouse that has stood since the 12th century but over time has been reconstructed. It stands as the main lighthouse of the harbour and is an iconic landmark of the city. After the tower of Hercules and the Kopu lighthouse, it is the oldest in the world. A large icon of the city of Genoa is present on one side, and the top is crowned with a large glass light. Standing at 76m high it towers over the surrounding area and can be seen for miles.</string>
    <!--Genoa-->
    ////////////////
    <!--About app-->
    <string name="about_app_1">\tI am Suyunov Lazizjon and I am 24.</string>
    <string name="about_app_2">\tI am from Uzbekistan, Samarkand </string>
    <string name="about_app_3">\tNow I am studying my master degree in Rome Italy, in University of Sapienza, in field of Transport System Engineering</string>
    <string name="about_app_4">\tAt the same time I am attending to the extra course by Android developing to the GITA Academy and this app is my second app in the second week.</string>
    <string name="about_app_5">\tIn this app I want to give a quick direction to the tourists who want to visit to Italy.</string>
    <string name="about_app_6">\tI took this information from Wikipedia and other web sites.</string>
    <string name="about_app_7">\tThanks for using this app</string>
    <!--About app-->

    <!--Names-->
    <string name="name_0">General information</string>
    <string name="name_1">Rome</string>
    <string name="name_2">Milan</string>
    <string name="name_3">Turin</string>
    <string name="name_4">Naples</string>
    <string name="name_5">Bologna</string>
    <string name="name_6">Florence</string>
    <string name="name_7">Vatican</string>
    <string name="name_8">Pisa</string>
    <string name="name_9">Venice</string>
    <string name="name_10">Sicily</string>
    <string name="name_11">Genoa</string>
    <string name="name_12">About app</string>
    <!--Names-->

</resources>